MK
ONE
Alabama, Arkansas I do love my ma and pa Not that way that I do love you
Well, holy moly, me oh my You're the apple of my eye Girl, I've never loved one like you
Man, oh man, you're my best friend, I'm screaming too, there's nothing there, there ain't nothing there I need
For hot and heavy, month and five, I chop and can't in Jesus Christ, very nothing please be more than me
Oh, let me come home, hold this way that I'm with you
Lord, I'm coming home
I follow you into the park, prove the jungle, prove the dark, girl I never loved one like you
I'm moat and moat and water falls, alleyways and pay for cause, I've been here the way that I do
That's true, that I'm here until we win, we're done, we're put on the summer night, never knew we'd be sweeter than we'd be
And in the day to run a pre-lack, it's only you and me, should you stop and let's sing
Oh, let me come home, hold this way that I'm with you
Oh, let me come home
J
I was there to do you remember that day you fell out of my window?
I sure do, you came jumping out after me
Well, you fell out of the concrete, nearly broke your ass and you were bleeding all over the place
And I brushed you out for the house, put your remember there?
Yes, I did
Well, it's something I never told you about that night
What if you saw me?
While you were sitting at the back seat, smug for the cigarette you thought was gonna be your last
I was falling deep deep deep in love with you
And I never wanted to lose you
Oh, let me come home, hold this way that I'm with you
Oh, yes, I am home, hold this way that I'm alone with you
And I never wanted to lose you
Oh, let me come home, hold this way that I'm with you